right moving on to module one and start here what counts is your first dollar this is fairly obvious
what isn't obvious is all those steps along the way right you have to have the service available
you have to be able to explain the service clearly to a customer that might not understand
any of it they just understand the need for it as well as a product right as well as the sales
aspect of it all the way to getting them to you know whether it's a bank transfer whether it's
putting your card information or it's a lemonade stand you're getting cash or a in-person square
payment however you're accepting those payments all the way from service to all right they paid
me now what right we're gonna talk about that side of the fence right now here is a what I had talked
about of the repeatable system here what can you do who is your audience how do I package my service or
product together I always recommend multiple packages outreach how do I reach out to my
customers how do I even know who they are what does that conversation start to look like how do I deal
with sales calls how do I deal with closing and delivering that onboarding experience for your
customers and then review it right whether it went well whether it went badly how do I review learn from
that repeat the process right do if on the review do I need to change the skill a little bit do I need
to change the offer a little bit do I need to change that first outreach message whatever it is cold email
text message DM whatever it is any of these aspects upon review I need to change some of it right
why this matters to side hustlers you know whether you're a side hustler whether you're a full-blown
multi-million dollar business this foundation is going to help build the piping the furnish on the
building so to speak it's gonna make your business look a little prettier it's gonna make your sales
process repeatable also so if you haven't already right you are the entrepreneur who doesn't have the
service yet who doesn't have all of this mapped out stop it the course right here and fill this out
pick your primary skill to find the painful problem who is your audience for it write your one-liner offer
it should be one line it shouldn't be a whole paragraph that you have to explain because people
are not gonna take the time to do their own research they kind of want I mean maybe they will
but you want to spoon feed them right problem solution problem here's why we solve the problem
whatever that is it should shouldn't be long and figure out your audience and I'm sure there are
people in your phone in your DMs however you find them through Google Maps Google search however you find
your potential clients get five of them I get 10 get 15 get 20 and then send out messages each one
personalized to each individual potential customer this is almost like sending out your resume to a
thousand different companies you want to tailor it to the specific company and send it out to them
you don't want it like completely general that's you want them to feel like you reached out to them
for a reason and you should right don't make them just feel like that you should do exactly that so
stop here if you haven't already done this for your business already or you already have it this is
helpful just to you know as an exercise continuing on kind of the same aspect and I think this is the
most important part simplicity wins this shouldn't be an over complicated conversation this shouldn't
be an over complicated message that you need to send out if you do and you'll see that getting them on
the phone is a difficult journey what am I saying on the phone right how do I establish value how do I
explain my product how do I push the customer towards me how do I differentiate myself from my
competitors these are all potentially like intentional as well as like
from your first dollar and I think the most important part here is going to be simplicity wins
right you want this to be a repeatable process you don't want to have separate snowflake conversations
with every single client I'm sure you will get to that point but for now at least your first package
however you want to package those services those products should be repeatable right you
want to ensure that your first DM your first message outwards is simple it should be tailored to the
specific customer and you should do a little research on them right you want to make sure the sales
conversation and you're going to realize that it's a long journey to get there is repeatable right
how do I differentiate myself from my competitors how do I highlight my service how do I show it off in
a portfolio if they're over the phone how do I tailor my messaging to a specific type of customer all of
these things should happen quite quickly and the customer doesn't really need to realize that that's what
you're doing right you don't need to say the exact words of this is how I differentiate myself from
my competitors you say something along the lines of maybe this is what everyone else is doing right
and here's why we're different some you know subtle cues within the conversation that the customer is
going to pick up that you need to practice more than likely stop here module two next
you